{
    "subject": "resource/Stepping_Out:_The_Very_Best_of_Joe_Jackson",
    "predicate": "ontology/artist",
    "object": "resource/Joe_Jackson_(musician)",
    "human_readable": "Joe Jackson is the artist of Stepping Out: The Very Best of Joe Jackson.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9834960699081421,
            "question": "Who is the artist behind the album 'Stepping Out: The Very Best of Joe Jackson'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8082542419433594,
            "question": "Is Joe Jackson a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5466027855873108,
            "question": "Does this album contain a selection of Joe Jackson's best work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.528557300567627,
            "question": "What kind of music might Joe Jackson perform?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42777928709983826,
            "question": "What could be some popular themes in Joe Jackson's music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3995364308357239,
            "question": "Where might you find more information about Joe Jackson and his music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32879477739334106,
            "question": "What is the title of the album by Joe Jackson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28077059984207153,
            "question": "Can you think of any other albums by Joe Jackson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.255490243434906,
            "question": "What does 'Stepping Out' likely suggest about the album's content?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.02746952697634697,
            "question": "Would you expect to find a variety of songs on this album?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Joe Jackson is the artist of Stepping Out: The Very Best of Joe Jackson.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7482_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does 'Stepping Out' likely suggest about the album's content?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7482_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you think of any other albums by Joe Jackson?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7482_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the title of the album by Joe Jackson?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7482_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7482_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7482_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7482_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7482_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7482_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7482_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7482_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7482_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7482_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7482_79.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can confirm that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe triple is supported by the documents. Specifically, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7482/re-ranker-msmarco/29.txt mentions Joe Jackson as the artist who wrote and performed the song \"Steppin' Out\", which is part of the album \"Joe Jackson - Stepping Out: The Very Best Of Joe Jackson\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provided contain information about Joe Jackson and his album \"Stepping Out: The Very Best Of Joe Jackson,\" which supports the statement that Joe Jackson is the artist of this album."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}